ANGEL CAMARGO



adcamargo10@gmail.com



https://acamargoportfolio.netlify.app/



C1 - ENGLISH LEVEL

ABOUT ME

Graduated as a software engineer at Universidad Rafael Belloso Chacin. having more than 4 years learning, and 1 year of demonstrable experience creating web apps, coding mainly in modern JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, SQL/NOSQL DBs, PHP 8.O, Laravel 9, Tailwindcss, Bootstrap, HTML and CSS, constantly learning. Good teamworker with an impeccable reputation as a programmer.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSIDAD RAFAEL **BELLOSO CHACIN**

Software Engineering, Nov 2022

UDEMY

PHP and Laravel Developer -MernStack Developer, and others.

2021 - 2022 - 2023

SANTA ANA DE JESUS

HighSchool Diploma Oct 2018 - Jul 2018

EXPERIENCE

BLUECARIBU - (CONTRACT/REMOTE)

FullStack Web Developer creating multiple web projects March 2023 - Present

bluecaribu !*

- We are creating an app from scratch using JavaScript (react, node, socket.io, and more) and storing data in 2 databases.
- I have created some new features and updated other functionalities previously built.
- I fixed some bugs debugging functions of the app.
- Fast learner and problem solver.

ALFA CO SAC - PERU (FREELANCER)

FullStack Web Developer creating JavaScript/PHP app and other features for ALFA CO SAC

Jul 2022 - Present

CXAlfa Co

- I made an API REST to make the connection between a mobile app and a database, using JavaScript/PHP.
- I created an administrative app from zero satisfying client needs using JavaScript/PHP.
- Making new features and fixing bugs.
- I created the entire database from scratch using MySQL and connecting db and client with PHP and JavaScript.